Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I've prepared three non-electronic games for you.
Let's start with the game called Ha!
Raw oats, raw gummies, raw eggs, raw gummies, raw gadgets, raw eggs.
You're a little glitchy, aren't you?
Nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah...
Dad.
The correct answer is A!
Hey!
I win this game of ha-ha!
Wow!
Now, I'd like to play a game of meow meow meow!
Meow meow meow!
The meow meow game!
Oh, yes!
Me and Jun-kun can understand...
First of all, there is a theme.
For example, there are animals and countries.
Then let's play it as a country.
Let's say it's a country.
For example, I'll do it now.
NyanNyan
Oh, I understand that.
I don't think you understand a little bit.
Nyan Nyan Nyan
No, no, no.
It means...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Jun-kun, jun-kun, jun-kun...
Switch already.
I'll do it now, assuming that's the name of the country.
Nyan-nyan
It's like, "What's this?
Japan
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, so that's how it is. Oh, you mean like that.
Like Japan
This is a guessing game
So you have to say all the country names in Nya
but you have to guess what is said in Nya.
If you can guess what it is, you get 1 point.
I see.
Well, it's pretty easy.
Let's try it.
Let's see.
There are some rules.
The player who plays the cat must...
Let's say Jun plays the cat.
We'll play two cards.
Put a theme card in the deck.
Turn over a card from the deck
and reads out the theme of the next card that comes up.
For example, if it's this one...
Then it's not here.
Then, say something starting with "here".
Let's see...
miaow
Okay, I see.
Mr. Zo...
I thought so too, Mr. Zo
The correct answer is zombie.
That's what I mean.
It's hard to play games with Chonkle.
I don't think I'm going to win anymore.
We're playing a game where we're at zero points and then the next one does it.
This is fun.
Let's play Meow Meow Rock, Paper, Paper Scissors.
Meow meow rock-paper-scissors.
Meow-meow rock-paper-scissors.
Meow!
You're the best at this.
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
Meow, meow, meow, meow. Meow.
Okay, then. Knock-knock.
Last meow is...
I'll be the cat.
Okay, I'll pull.
Come on.
Something warm.
It's pretty hard to find an apartment.
Here you go.
Hey...
Hey... hey... hey...
Difficult?
Difficult
Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne.
Ah! I got it, I got it, I got it!
I got it!
You got it?
Here we go.
Miso soup
Ew.
Ew, that's disgusting!
Isn't this hard?
I didn't expect it to come out.
Don't even think about it yet.
It's supposed to be warm.
Iron.
Iron, iron, iron.
Iron. Iron.
A hundred different.
He didn't say anything.
I'm sorry, that's weird.
The correct answer was miso soup.
Oh, my God.
That's what miso soup is all about.
Here we go!
The names of monuments and buildings... I'm so excited... I'm going to say it!
I only know the essentials... World Heritage?
Let's just answer the questions we can answer. Let's go with the one that we can answer to. We can do it, can't we?
What kind of confidence do you have in us?
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow.
I can't do it.
Oh!
You don't know?
Seriously?
Nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah.
You want someone who understands, right?
Oh, OK.
Byodoin News
Byodoin News.
I was with you.
The correct answer is Byodoin Press.
Oh!
That's great.
Here we go.
I really should have gone for something harder.
I should have gone all the way around the world.
Oh, my God.
You're not supposed to be nice.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
That's it.
I feel so smart.
I'm having fun.
That's good.
Okay, I'll go.
I'm in.
Yeah!
Aah!
What? Kind of beans?
What? I thought they were limited.
We'll get it in time.
OK, here we go!
Squishy squishy squishy!
Nya nya nya!
Not yet, Jun-kun! Not yet, Jun-kun.
Maybe this will give us something
Maybe something else will turn up.
What? I said I thought it was a bean!
Nyonya nyonya!
Seriously?
Are you sure?
Saya end
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
That's a tough one.
Pistachio.
Oh, beans. Pistachios are beans.
Beans.
Game on!
No, no, no, no. That's not the game.
That's not the game. They're beans.
Let's do it again. It's so frustrating. It's so frustrating.
Let's take turns.
Let's have a turn!
Let's play again in my house!
It's the same as before.
I'm not good at rock-paper-scissors-paper either.
It starts from the beginning
Oh, oh, revenge.
Yes, yes...
Is it decided?
Here we go.
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
I've decided.
Wait, which one is it?
Is this okay? Can I do it?
I'm good.
more water
More money. increased amount of money
Oooh.
The correct answer was rising water.
Wow, rising water!
Let's go.
This game is fun!
The name of the instrument.
Here we go!
Meow Meow Meow Meow
Let's try one more time to make it clearer
Meow meow meow meow meow!
I don't know any more harmonica
Yes, yes...
What's that?
Trumbone.
How about...
Contrabass.
No, it's hard!
Oh, it's so hard!
I don't know!
I don't know.
It's the kind of thing that only comes to me when you tell me.
Like the trumpet.
You've got to be kidding me.
You don't know what you're doing.
A game you enjoy playing.
It's so close, it's so close, it's so close.
I'd like to win.
Okay, let's move on.
Yes, sir.
Yes!
Flower name
Flower name.
Oh, this one...
Oh, no!
Here we go.
Yes!
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
Wait a minute.
You just said that in the really nya...
meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow!
I understand now.
Huh?
You know what I mean.
So that's all it sounds like now.
Yeah.
I'm not saying "meow" anymore.
Oh, no.
Churi.
Say it again.
Oh, you're right.
Just in time.
I said it.
Meow.
Yes.
Meow!
Hey!
I couldn't do anything!
Wait, let's go again!
Let's go again.
Jun-kun, they're done talking.
They're done.
Let's go.
I'm done.
It's good.
Here we go!
Nyonya nyonya! Nyonya nyonya!
I only play the trumpet.
Is there a lot of them in the world?
There's one from here already.
What? What?
I see you.
Meow meow meow?
There's a meow meow?
Yeah, I see it.
I'm not coming out either.
Skinhead.
It's Jun-kun.
But he's Jun-kun.
You're right. I don't know if it's true.
Maybe he can see the trumpet.
Trumpet?
Yes, that's right.
Plastic.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
So, the real cat is...
Kaname!
Wow, that's amazing!
Meow!
I knew it was because Roo-chan won!
It's a dog.
It's a dog!
Now, next...
I'd like to play "Nanja Monja".
I've heard a lot about it, but I don't know the rules.
I hear that a lot.
Really?
Of the three games today, this is the only one I know the rules of.
Nanja, Nanja, Nanja...
That's right, Jun.
What the heck...
Well, let me explain the rules.
When you open the card like this...
A lot of cards with characters on them come out like this.
Like this.
Each character has a different name.
You name them.
I see. I see.
One by one, like this.
So, for example, this orange character craft, you name it.
Hmmm...
Strong Dooce.
Ginger.
Yes, Strong Peter.
I named him.
This one is Strong Peter.
And we'll name them like this, one by one.
Like this.
Hendricks Robertson.
Brother seconds.
Hendricks...
Hendricks Robertson.
Robertson.
Well, well, well... I'm going to name them like this.
And then Hendricks Robertson came out of it.
And then...
I'm going to call this boy's name the moment he comes out of this
Hendricks Robertson.
The person who can say it the quickest...
I've got a stack of cards here as a guard.
I'll bring you all the cards I've got in this deck.
That's why we say the person with the most cards wins.
Whoever has the most cards wins.
One more rule.
Let's do it again.
There's a rule for advanced players, but today we're going to incorporate it.
So...
Hendricks Robertson is here.
"Hendricks Robertson, you got it!
And then the next one...
And then this character, same thing again.
And then the same one came... but not Hendricks Robertson.
Say "What the hell is that?
What the hell is this?
If you see the same character in a row, say "Nanjamonja," not "Hendricks Robertson. I don't mean that name.
I mean, how many people can remember that name?
The important point of this game is to see how well you can remember the name.
That's the important point of this game.
Okay, let's play.
Who would like to start?
I can't do anything good so far.
I'll go first.
All right.
I think I have the upper hand here.
I'll go first.
Okay, first one is this girl.
Ah!
Kosaka, what was her name again?
Strong Peter.
Strong Peter, No. 2.
Let's start from the beginning.
This one's really hard!
No. 2.
Wow!
Avocado, Avocado, Avocado, Avocado!
Avocado, avocado, avocado, avocado, avocado!
Here we go.
Here you go.
Mop?
Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Okay, okay.
Pineapple.
Yeah, moo-ya-moo-ya-moo-ya-moo-ya-moo-ya
Moo goo goo goo goo, Peter.
Avocado with a shaggy head
Avocado, Avocado, Avocado, Avocado, Avocado
Shhh!
Why didn't I tell you?
Shai.
New character! New Character Arrived
Yubari Melon
Far away from Hokkaido
Mop!
Reset?
I forgot my mop.
Furball.
Don't call me that.
Masaya Sakuragi.
Masaya will get mad if he sees me too.
No, it's pink, then.
Easy to see, easy to see.
That's right, that's right.
I see.
It's not pink, so what's the explanation?
Sunshine Ink.
That's me.
Oh, shit! Oh, no, it's not a rag.
A hairball!
Furball!
I made a mistake.
A hairball. That's right.
It's right. It's not a mop, it's not a rag.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, now caramel.
Caramel.
There we go.
Mash.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, I see what you're getting at.
Long legs.
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Then what is it?
What is it?
Whoa!
Wow!
No, it's good!
You're good!
Ow!
Nice!
In this case, it's a what-the-hell-are-you-doing?
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Oh, no, I'm weak, what a jerk!
No, no, no, I won again.
Strong! I'm strong.
Please.
Here we go.
Wow, cool.
This guy's a real charmer.
Supermodel.
Hey, you're early.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh...
Um...
Let's see...
Winter is here. Let's eat oranges.
That sucks.
Ha-ha-ha
Uh-oh.
Moo moo melon.
Melon, melon, melon.
Munchy melon. Mr. Motsubutsu Melon
Oh!
It's Masaya Sakuragi.
You almost saw him.
That's what I'm going to do.
Straw.
Oh, straws.
Where do you want it?
Where do you want it? The straw.
Oh, that's a blur.
Oh, you're not getting it.
You're not here.
Let's see...
Pistachio
Pistachio.
Yeah, pistachio.
Which one do you like? I don't see any.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm forgetting everything right now.
This is a long one.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
It's been a long time.
I've got a lot of this stuff.
I'll be happy when I hear something I've heard.
This is fun.
Oh, here we go again.
Well...
I don't have a name to give you anymore.
Lots of leg hair.
It looks like it, because it's written in crayon.
I hate saying this.
Oh, there's a new character.
Hey, Mom.
I think it's good. I think it's good.
Oh, no.
Yoshizawa then.
Yoshizawa.
This is me.
I have a lot of leg hair.
I don't want to tell you.
I got this one.
It's getting stronger.
I'm getting stronger.
Shall we count then? Shall we count?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty, twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three.
Wow, he's really strong.
So we've played three games. It was a lot of fun.
What's the result? There was a game called "What?
There was a game called "Crafting." It was something like 3 points, 5 points...
Kaname won the "Meow Meow" game.
Kaname won the "Meow Meow" game and Kaname won the "Meow Meow" game...
Oh no!
Then we were happy.
And Jun-kun was sad.
This would be a great game to play with the family!
I really think, let's play this backstage, instead of playing phone games.
I can't keep up with you.
It'll be fun! If you have time...
If we have time, let's play some more games and film it.
Let's do it with everyone... I'll be happy if we can do it with everyone!
I'm looking forward to seeing you next time!
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
Baman, that's it!